https://romanrunners.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyONLINE PRIVACY
POLICY AGREEMENTRoman Runners is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those individuals that visit our website and make use of our online facilities and services accurate, confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with Roman Runners Club of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards.THEREFORE, this Privacy
Policy Agreement shall apply to Roman Runners, and thus it shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof.
Through the use of Roman
Runners you are herein consenting to the
following data procedures expressed within this agreement.Collection of InformationThis website collects various types of information, such as:Information automatically collected when visiting our website, which may include cookies, third party tracking technologies and server logs.We may also gather information about the type of browser you are using, IP address or type of operating system to assist us in providing and maintaining superior quality service.It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any website you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand the way in which other websites garner, make use of and share information collected.Use of Information CollectedRoman Runners may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need  and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available  to you from romanrunners.com . Roman Runners may also be in contact with you with regards to completing  surveys  and/or  research  questionnaires  related  to your  opinion  of  current  or potential future services that may be offered.Roman Runners does not  now, nor  will it in the future,  sell,  rent  or lease  any  of our customer lists and/or names to any third parties.Roman Runners may deem it necessary to follow websites and/or pages that our users may frequent in an effort to gleam what types of services and/or products may be the most popular to customers or the general public.Roman Runners may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:•             Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon Quip Web Designs and/or our website;•   Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of Roman Runners; and•       Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of quipwebdesigns.com and/or the general public.Children Under Age of 13Roman Runners does not knowingly  collect  personal  identifiable  information  from  children under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently  collected  on  anyone under  the  age of thirteen  (13),  we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system’s  database.  Anyone under the  age of thirteen  (13)  must  seek  and  obtain  parent  or guardian permission to use this website.Unsubscribe or Opt-OutAll  users  and/or  visitors  to  our  website  have the  option  to  discontinue  receiving communication  from  us and/or  reserve  the  right  to discontinue  receiving  communications  by way  of email  or  newsletters.  To discontinue  or  unsubscribe  to our  website  please  send an email   that   you   wish   to   unsubscribe   to   shirley@quipwebdesigns.com.   If    you   wish   to unsubscribe or opt-out from any third party websites, you must go  to that specific website to unsubscribe and/or opt-out.Links to Other Web SitesOur website does contain  links  to affiliate  and  other  websites. Roman Runners does not claim  nor  accept  responsibility  for  any privacy  policies,  practices  and/or  procedures  of other such websites.  Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors  to be aware  when they  leave our  website  and  to  read  the  privacy  statements  of  each and  every  website  that  collects personally identifiable information. The afore mentioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by our website.SecurityRoman Runners shall endeavor and shall take  every  precaution  to  maintain  adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user’s personal information under our control.T h e company    also   uses Secure   Socket   Layer  (SSL)   for   authentication   and   private communications  in an  effort  to build users’  trust  and  confidence  in the internet  and  website use by providing  simple  and  secure  access and  communication of credit  card  and personal information.Changes to Privacy Policy AgreementRoman Runners reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those change to our website homepage at Roman Runners.com, so that our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under  what circumstances,  if any,  we may disclose  such information.  If at any point in time Roman Runners decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from  that which  was stated  when this  information  was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information  in this  separate manner.Acceptance of TermsUsing this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement.  If you are not in agreement with ourterms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our sites. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.How to Contact UsIf you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website, please feel free to contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing address.Email: shirley@quipwebdesigns.com
